Arjun Krishna

+918848661970 +919539641476 arjunkrishna.office@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/arjun-krishna-k

Summary:

I am an IIT Roorkee alumnus currently working as a software developer at adobe. I'm passionate about web, mobile and desktop software development. Through my work experience and projects I have understood to adopt oops design principles on single and multithreaded workflows. I would love to work with companies working on challenging products and ideas.

Education:

Year	Degree	Institution	Percentage
2016-2019	B. Tech. Electronics Major, Computer science Minor	IIT Roorkee	93.86%
2015-2016	Senior high school (12th Grade)	Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan	97%
2014	High school (10 th Grade)	Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan	100%

Experience:

Duration	Role	Institution	Description
Jun 2019 – Present	Member of technical staff	Adobe Systems	Developed Genshop which is Adobe's in-house deep learning python library for Generative models primarily GANs. Worked on CPU (single and multithreaded) and GPU workflows of Adobe Color Engine (ACE)
Dec 2017 – Jan 2018(2 months)	Research Assistant	IIT Roorkee	Worked on Action Recognition with feature fusion.
May 2018 - July 2018 (3 months)	Research Intern	Adobe Systems	Interned with Big Data Experience Lab, Adobe Research, Bengaluru.

Skills:

- Programming: C++, Python, Java, JavaScript C, Objective C, MATLAB
- Databases: SQL, MongoDb
- Frameworks: React.js, Node.js, Android SDK, TensorFlow, Pytorch, DirectX12, Metal, Microsoft SDK
- Developer tools: Git, Perforce, Visual Studio, Android Studio, XCode, PyCharm

Projects:

- Express flowcharts android app
- Video segment copy detection
- Text detection in natural scenes
- Google chrome extension to caption images using RCNN

Achievements:

- Best B.Tech. Project Award IIT Roorkee received from director IIT Roorkee.
- Winner Adobe Shark Tank event.
- KVPY National Scholarship 2015 Fellow.
- Cleared First Stage of CODEFUNDO 2015 conducted by Microsoft.
- District topper of AISSCE (All India Senior School Certificate Examination) 2015 certificate received from education minister India.
- Cleared First Level of International Chemistry Olympiad 2015.

Domain Knowledge:

Android App Development, Website Development, Storage Scalability, System Design, Computer Vision, Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Image processing, Color Management

Languages Known:

English, Hindi, Malayalam

References:

Vinod Pankajakshan Assistant Professor Electronics Department, IIT Roorkee vinodfec@iitr.ac.in 07409726873 Saikat Chakrabarthy
Computer Scientist
Adobe Systems
chakraba@adobe.com